How to open a UB
Marlboro's Designer supports you to open a UB according to the shape of the board.
Here I added a seat in advance.
Right-click on the 2D board window or 3D window title bar, and then select Open UB Editor.
You can see that there are two labels at the bottom of the 2D window.
You can quickly switch between the 2D window and the UB editor window again.
Right-click on the blank area in the UB window, and you can place the UB in the 2D board.
Tips 1. Before you start editing UB, it is best to place the UB in the 2D board first.
This is to have the correct ratio between UBs and to organize the UB position.
You can use the automatic UB fill tool in the upper left corner.
Fill here, enter the value, and determine the distance between the UB pieces.
Select the optimized layout, and press and hold to select whether to allow rotation and whether to set the shrink ratio.
It will automatically move the selected UB pieces to the appropriate size and place them in the first line.
Select the UB pieces and right-click.
You can turn the UB pieces horizontally or vertically, and you can also align them.
Then right-click and place the UB pieces at 0-1.
Enter the number in the dialog box at the bottom.
Determine the distance between the UB pieces and the edge of the UB frame.
This operation will mix the selected UB pieces together and fill it to the first UB line.
Tips 2. If you want to edit the UB on the back and side of the board,
First, change the texture display on the 3D window to the Rumi texture surface.
You must change it here to identify the UB on the back and side.
Select the board, adjust the height, increase the thickness, zoom, and mm.
This will determine the width of the UB on the side.
Pull the element edit button to the bottom.
Open the UB expansion bar and select the UB you want to appear.
Tips 3. Select the UB on the back and side.
At this time, the UB on the back and side has appeared in the UB editor.
The UB on the back is defaulted to overlap with the UB on the front.
The UB on the side is defaulted to squeeze out along the edge of the UB on the front.
Tips 2. Try the distance between the UB pieces and the distance between the UB pieces and the UB frame.
The two numbers written below should be greater than the thickness of the fabric.
In case of opening the UB on the side, there will be a cross overlap between the UB pieces.
If you plan to use different materials on the front and back,
press Shift and A to select all the UB pieces on the front.
Use the Move UB tool to move the UB on the front to other lines.
Tips 3. Click on the item you want to use.
In the property editor, in the property, switch to the back cover page.
To cancel the selection of materials with the same material on the front,
you can click on the material on the back here.
Tips 4. Select the material on the side.
Tips 5. Select the material on the side.
At this time, the UB editing is basically complete.
Click on the small ball in the upper left corner to see the different types of postage effects again.
Tips 6. Use the baking pattern tool to bake and save the postage you need.
Tips 7. Use the UB quick photo tool to screenshot and save the UB quick photo you need.
That's all for today.
Thanks for watching.
See you in the next video.